<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[My Life]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[My Life]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/david-bedinghaus/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2016 13:02:53 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/david-bedinghaus/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[David]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>David</h1><p>My website is an ongoing record of my culinary based ideas and inspiration associated with product I have developed for various clients. I have been a professional culinarian for more than 30 years and more than 20 of those years have been outside the USA, my birth place. My work has taken me to many bizarre and interesting places and searching for new eatable idea's I can learn from and use to bring forward for the world to see and enjoy.  Through this process of perpetual creative stimulation, documentation and sharing I hope these works will show young cooks and chefs that the creative process is infinite. The limitations are only born in ones own mind and that simplicity is more widely recognized and understood than complexity.  Knowing what is foundational and what is fad is the key to success, but is not to say that you shouldn't experience and learn from that which is less understood or not accepted in the culinary world as they are equally challenging, exciting and one day will be recognized, but when?</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/538656cae61b726f6944f071971c9e5aacc6f32e.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/david-bedinghaus/david/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2a1c7632-2eee-4174-bccb-0748a3fecd4a</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2016 13:01:18 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>